# MIRANDA THOMPSON

#### **OBJECTIVE**

I am embarking into a new career of web development and looking for the opportunity to grow with an innovative company.

#### **SKILLS & ABILITIES**

I have background in electric and medical offices as well as restaurant, barista, and retail experience. I have extensive customer service skills in addition to being organized and task/goal oriented. I can use Microsoft Office programs such as Excel and Word as well as Adobe. I work well with others, possess leadership skills and have volunteered for over 10 years with the schools and other organizations in the community. I am hands-on, like to learn new tasks, and see them through to completion. I enjoy writing articles as well as drafting templates and letters. I am also CPR, AED, first aid and BBP certified, as well as a State of Oregon Notary. I have completed the University of Oregon's coding bootcamp to become a full-stack web developer learning basic HTML, CSS, JavaScript, API's to Node, Mysql, React, No Sql, PWA's, computer science and much more.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### COOS-CURRY ELECTRIC COOPERATIVE, BROOKINGS, OR

#### **Lead Member Services Representative** August 2017-Present

Serving members of the electric cooperative by taking payments, generating, and processing service orders for connects, disconnects, meter changes, new service, and various maintenance requests as well as reporting outages, balancing drawers and daily deposits, billing and adjustments to accounts, and more. Using programs such as Excel, Word, SEDC UPN, Catalyst mapping, etc. Communicating and working with all internal departments from operations, engineering to corporate services, and dispatching when needed. Editing pre-bill for 7 cycles, running bank and credit card drafts, weekly collections and refunds, overseeing work of MSR's. Invested with community involvement committee with CCEC, the Benefits Committee as well as marketing and recruiting for Co-op connections program.

#### **BELL & WHISTLE COFFEE HOUSE, BROOKINGS, OR**

Barista January 2017-August 2017

Greeted customers, took orders, made espresso drinks, baked and made food items, took phone orders, counted and managed a cash register, submitted deposits, trained new employees, and performed inventory. I worked opening, mid-day and closing shifts.

#### **EXPERIENCE CONT...**

#### SUTTER MEDICAL GROUP (INTERNAL MEDICINE), SACRAMENTO, CA

Medical Assistant, Receptionist, Referrals November 1999-April 2001

Answered multi-line telephone for an eight-physician internal medicine office, scheduled appointments, posted payments, greeted patients. Roomed and triaged patients, took vital signs, administered injections, assisted doctors with procedures, called in refills and prescriptions. Obtained insurance authorization for procedures, labs and specialty physicians, faxed pertinent chart notes, made appointments for patients and notified them. Pulled charts and filed new chart information, made chart copies for other physicians or patients, always maintaining patient confidentiality.

#### **EDUCATION**

LinkedIn trainings on customer service, Microsoft teams, Excel and more. SEDC courses pertaining to their programs, Myra Golden customer service training. Coding camps and development courses online.

**UNIVERSITY OF OREGON: CODING BOOTCAMP WEB DEVELOPMENT-ONLINE** Rigorous course teaching fundamentals of full-stack web development.

# BOSTON REED COMPANY-CHARLES A JONES SKILLS & BUSINESS CENTER, SACRAMENTO, CA, MEDICAL ASSISTING & PHLEBOTOMY CERTIFICATION

I worked full time and attended this night class to obtain my certificate for Medical Assisting and Phlebotomy. I was also required to do an externship and complete an additional course to obtain certification through Sutter Medical.

#### CASTLE ROCK CHARTER SCHOOL, CRESCENT CITY, CA, HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA

For high school, I was home schooled, attended 2 different high schools and finished credits at Castle Rock Charter School.

#### COMMUNICATION

I am involved with the CCEC Co-op Connections program, which relies heavily on communication with other teammates, local businesses and the national Co-op connections leadership and group. This discount program needs participation from local business partners, and all of Member Services in order to thrive. It is a project that I plan on developing further with my teammates and supervisor.

### **LEADERSHIP**

It was an honor to serve as a Steering Committee member for The Compassionate Friends Northwest Chapter (TCF) for 8 years. I facilitated meetings for the sibling group and filled in as facilitator for the parent group, helped with fundraisers and many events including an annual candle lighting ceremony and balloon release BBQ. I also wrote all the anniversary cards for the chapter during that time. I am currently engaged with the Coos Curry Electric Community Involvement Committee that is actively involved with events and participation in our communities. I also assist, as needed, with the CCE Charitable Foundation as well.

## **References Attached**

#### **REFERENCES**

MARIE COLEMAN, WAREHOUSE-COOS-CURRY ELECTRIC COOPERATIVE

541-661-1394

CINDY PEARE, SAFETY & LOSS ADMINISTRATOR-COOS-CURRY ELECTRIC COOPERATIVE

541-254-0696

GEORGIA COCKERHAM, RETIRED FINANCIAL ADVISOR-CHAPTER LEADER FOR TCF NORTHWEST

541-469-5814

WILSON HODGE, ENGINEERING AIDE II-COOS-CURRY ELECTRIC COOPERATIVE

541-260-5979

DAVE HOUSTON, BUSINESS OWNER-LATITUDE 42

702-274-8402

WILSON HODGE, ENGINEERING AIDE II-COOS-CURRY ELECTRIC COOPERATIVE

541-260-5979

**SHERRY STRAIN,** REAL ESTATE BROKER-CENTURY 21 AGATE REALTY

541-661-3993

# **Additional References Available Upon Request**